Trevor Leeman

▼ trevormleeman@gmail.com

(425) 308 8499

in LinkedIn

GitHub

Pallevue, WA, United States

Profile

2017 - 2019

2014 - 2017

Full Stack Web Developer and IT Professional with 5 years professional experience. Highly proficient with JavaScript and the DOM, HTML, CSS (SASS), TypeScript, React, Next.js, SQL, Git, and ColdFusion. Lover of all things frontend - currently building projects with Tailwind CSS! Solid understanding of the Client / Server Model, Chrome Dev Tools, and debugging web applications from the front and backend. Demonstrated ability to bring performant and accessible web applications from concept to reality.

Professional Experience	
01/2022 – Present	 Software Engineer, M3 USA Create new components and features for the mdlinx.com website using React, TypeScript, Next.js, GraphQL, Tailwind CSS, and Node.js. Work closely with a designer, transforming designs created in Zeplin to functional React components. Carry out research as necessary, generating informed opinions on open source libraries and leveraging them when appropriate. Review other engineers' code in GitHub.
06/2019 - 01/2022	 Web Application Developer, Everett Community College Designed, prototyped, and developed full stack web applications using ColdFusion, T-SQL, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. Thoughtfully developed with accessibility, security, cross browser compatibility, and mobile responsiveness in mind. Worked directly with stakeholders, planning and defining reqs for new apps. Troubleshot and resolved application bugs and server errors. Red Hat Linux and Windows Server configuration.
07/2018 - 06/2019	 Student Web Developer, Central Washington University Actively developed and maintained the cwu.edu website in an Agile Scrum environment. Led weekly development workshops to train and certify departmental content managers.
08/2016 - 07/2017	IT Help Desk Specialist, Everett Community College
Education	

Bachelor - Web Development and Database Administration,

Associate - Information Technology, Everett Community College

Central Washington University